- ObjectiveID: 99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99D_Yonas_A
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99D_MSQ_01
  RequiredAchievementId: 99C_MSQ_12||(99_MSQ_35&&!99_MSQ_56)
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: earringgreatcleavet5
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_title"
  Description: "@99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99D_MSQ_01_RescueWarden_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99D_Galahad_C
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99D_MSQ_02
  RequiredAchievementId: 99D_MSQ_01
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Headgear_40
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_title"
  Description: "@99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99D_MSQ_02_ClimbRuins_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99D_Yonas_B
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99D_MSQ_03
  RequiredAchievementId: 99D_MSQ_02
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Footwear_40
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_title"
  Description: "@99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99D_MSQ_03_ThorpeBackstory_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99D_Yonas_C
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99D_MSQ_04
  RequiredAchievementId: 99D_MSQ_03
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Weapons_40
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_title"
  Description: "@99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99D_MSQ_04_DestroyMines_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99D_Galahad_E
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99D_MSQ_05
  RequiredAchievementId: 99D_MSQ_04
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Handwear_45
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_title"
  Description: "@99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99D_MSQ_05_CrossBridge_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99D_Yonas_D
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99D_MSQ_06
  RequiredAchievementId: 99D_MSQ_05
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT4
  ItemRewardQty: 10.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_title"
  Description: "@99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99D_MSQ_06_DestroyPortals_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99D_Yonas_F
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99D_MSQ_07
  RequiredAchievementId: 99D_MSQ_06
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Chestwear_45
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_title"
  Description: "@99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99D_MSQ_07_PortalFight_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: Soul Trial
- ObjectiveID: 99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99D_Yash_F
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99D_MSQ_08
  RequiredAchievementId: 99D_MSQ_07
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: HoningStoneT4
  ItemRewardQty: 3.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_title"
  Description: "@99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99D_MSQ_08_ThorpeFight_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99D_Grace
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99D_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99D_MSQ_08 && !Archetype_Mercenary && !Archetype_Warmonger && !Archetype_Tracker && !Archetype_Musketeer && !Archetype_Occultist && !Archetype_Theurgist && !Archetype_Wanderer
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_50
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_title"
  Description: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_destroyer
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99D_Grace
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99D_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99D_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Warmonger
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_success_destroyer
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_50
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_title"
  Description: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_musketeer
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99D_Grace
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99D_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99D_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Musketeer
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_success_musketeer
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_50
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_title"
  Description: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_mystic
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99D_Grace
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99D_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99D_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Theurgist
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_success_mystic
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_50
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_title"
  Description: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_occultist
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99D_Grace
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99D_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99D_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Occultist
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_success_occultist
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_50
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_title"
  Description: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_ranger
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99D_Grace
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99D_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99D_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Tracker
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_success_ranger
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_50
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_title"
  Description: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_soldier
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99D_Grace
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99D_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99D_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Mercenary
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_success_soldier
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_50
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_title"
  Description: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_swordsman
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99D_Grace
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99D_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99D_MSQ_08 && Archetype_Wanderer
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_success_swordsman
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT4_Legwear_50
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_title"
  Description: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99D_MSQ_09_Outpost_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: ""
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99E_Sun_p1
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99D_MSQ_10
  RequiredAchievementId: 99D_MSQ_09
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT4
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_title"
  Description: "@99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_incomplete_a"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99D_MSQ_10_CaerDun_completion_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
